{
    "id": "04efba27f8c146b99613f7ef380ce10f",
    "title": "Is, Am, Are, Was, Were | Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "What …………… you doing at 7’O clock in the morning?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are",
                "were",
                "had"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ef83698d15ba457d8ee74efafb6a94c1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………….. sleeping when the telephone rang.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am",
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "aeead78a858e43d69d21ae6f44117e25"
        },
        {
            "question": "When you phoned  I …………… working in the garden.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am",
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f18e7725003e4748a4d4ccee5552aee4"
        },
        {
            "question": "When I got up this morning the sun ………….. shining.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "was"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1bcfe102e3d94a3e9644cb6b1c00a09f"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘Have you finished that report?’ ‘I ………………. working on it.’",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am",
                "was",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9eaa53f35c064fda915a37490679a623"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………….. painting all day yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am",
                "was",
                "had"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e1be12831c2d43d18fddf17cf8a258be"
        },
        {
            "question": "The children ……………….. playing video games.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are",
                "is",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dbf945ba3a4640c295f43193c2cd0c7c"
        },
        {
            "question": "She …………………. working in the garden.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "has"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b170c03bc722440081cff49abb832bef"
        },
        {
            "question": "The teacher ……………. evaluating the answer sheets.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "has"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b74a257fe6224eb09e5d94f916451916"
        },
        {
            "question": "You can’t go out now. It …………….. raining cats and dogs.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "has",
                "was"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d1d3bbfc5e404aaaba3c072efa8e6761"
        }
    ]
}